{
    "id": "bf4437322cdd47968e5f0d147741c726",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I talked to the man ………………… bag was stolen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "whom",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1bc607e7b31946dbb8560285b8eeb9d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know ………………… he wants.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0bf22613e76f4ed3ac54247004e546c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is an ill wind ……………….. blows nobody good.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afb27403cfc7484d97e8aaffe44bfd0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "God helps those ………………… help themselves.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d7733cc21b8e4e71b8f8e3ae4aa1d6f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please try to understand ……………… I mean.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cfe17e99372741fbb6036153f90ec61a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The flowers ………………….. grow on the mountains are very beautiful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a1e07e000b2340bfba0131311fc78f84"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the only chapter in the book ………………… is worth reading.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d99bf53d8fa34feeac4771dc64a9db9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "All …………….. you say is certainly true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6f46c98c57b4b2fbccc64c3906530b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………….. dies for a noble cause lives forever.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4cd8567ebe3848a49c8078fc132efb94"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hope the little ………………… I have done has been useful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6a95c2283fad4611ab6204042e3b0f2a"
        }
    ]
}